[Visionary] 0day-sub
遠鑒字幕組製作
翻譯&校對   william2568 我問這瓜保熟麼 Sue牧師
一年2400次 一周44次 一天9次 每48分鐘 就有一宗銀行搶劫
這是全球銀行搶劫之都
洛杉磯
賊 巢
加迪納 南洛杉磯 早上 5:14
別 別 別 兄弟！我們不是衝著你們來的！想都別想！
No, no, no, bro! We're not here for you! Don't even think about it!
別動 他媽的！
Don't you move, motherfucker!
手離武器遠點兒 兄弟！你他媽的給我放鬆！
Hands away from the weapon, bro! Fucking relax!
我是3170 我們被圍住了
3170. We're being held up.
穿甲子彈已經上膛了！
Armor piercing rounds are chambered in this firearm!
別逼我開火
Please don't be the asshole who forces me to use them.
腳從腳踏板上拿開
Take your foot off the gas,
按下開門鍵 然後從車裏出來
press the unlock button, and step out of the vehicle,
否則我會強行把你拖出來！
or we will forcibly remove you!
快點 給我滾出來
Fucking do it! Now!
這是你逼我的 動手
Your choice! Go!
他媽的
What the fuck!
他媽的他是去摸他的槍了！
He fucking went for his gun.
他媽的他是把咖啡給灑了！
He spilled his fucking coffee.
霍 桑
見鬼！
Shit.
加迪納 30秒
Gardena, 30 seconds out.
收到
Copy.
剩下30秒了 快點！
Thirty out. Hustle!
- 炸開它 - 準備好了
- Pop it. - Ready.
上！
Man on!
都他媽沒時間了！
Out of fucking time.
準備好交火
Prepare to engage.
右邊有敵人
Contact right!
100米 火力壓制
Range 100. Suppressive fire.
左邊有敵人！
Contact left!
1097出動 洛杉磯警察已到現場
Dispatch, 10-97. LAPD is on scene.
我們遭到了火力壓制！
We are under heavy fire!
操你媽的！
Fuck!
他媽的
Motherfucker!
我來掩護你
Whoa, whoa. I got you. I got you.
快走 快走
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
他媽的剛剛是怎麼回事？
What the fuck was that?
你看見他去碰槍了?
Did you see him go for his gun?
我不知道 我只看到博斯科把他崩了
I don't know. I just saw Bosco lit him up.
第二個路口左轉進入隧道
Take the second left into the tunnel.
順著機場 進入隧道
Hug the airport. Take the tunnel.
在多提右轉
Go right on Doty.
多提右轉
Right on Doty.
威明頓
確保你們管好你們的槍
Make sure you take care of those weapons.
不希望有槍走火
I don't want any accidental discharges.
- 你看著他說這話幹嘛？- 雷
- What are you looking at him for? - Ray.
我不是在跟他說 我是跟你說
I'm not talking to him. I'm talking to you.
剛剛他媽的到底怎麼回事？
What the fuck was that?
你他媽還搞砸什麼了？
What else did you fuck up, huh?
你確定回來的時候沒被跟蹤嗎？
You sure you were clean all the way home?
有尾巴嗎？
Catch any tails?
馬庫斯哪裏中槍了？
Where did Marcus take those rounds?
股動脈 他死定了
Femoral artery. He's done.
我們知道這行是有風險的
Well, we knew the risks.
突發狀況 我們處理好了 沒事兒了
Shit popped off. We handled it. That's it.
嘿 B
Hey, B.
回去那裏
Get back over there.
看看是誰接手了 可能是洛杉磯治安局
See who responded. It was probably LASD.
他們比加迪納警察職權大
They'll supersede Gardena,
但如果這次行動被立為重案 我們就有麻煩了
but if it's Major Crimes, we've got a problem.
都沒問題了吧？沒發現有GPS追蹤器吧？
All clear? No GPS?
有一個老款的 已經處理掉了
It's one of the old models, man. We good.
我們需要把禍給補上！
We've got to get this patched up.
需要乾淨利落！
We need this clean.
你還好嗎？
You good?
我們現在成了警察殺手了
We're cop killers now.
梅利曼
聖佩德羅
天！
Jesus Christ!
你嚇我一跳 寶貝 你不能那樣做
You scared the shit out of me, babe. Can't do that.
你現在在幹嘛？
What are you doing right now?
刪除最近的通話記錄？
You erasing your recent calls?
我的電話裏的？你什麼意思？
My phone? What do you mean?
我根本不會使用這個鬼東西 你知道的
I don't know how to work this fucking thing. You know that.
「我根本不會使用這個鬼東西 你知道的」
"I don't know how to work this fucking thing. You know that."
別裝了
Come on.
寶貝 我們現在真的要為這個吵架嗎？
Babe, we really have to go through this right now?
你去哪了？
Where you been?
早上6點了 你去哪了？
It's 6:00 a.m. Where have you been?
在工作？
Been at work?
監視？搶劫毒販？因為你全身都是脫衣舞孃味兒
Surveillance? Robbing drug dealers? Because you smell like a stripper.
我當然是在工作
Of course, I was at work.
那很奇怪 我收到了這條短信
It's funny 'cause I got this text.
什麼那麼性感啊？
What was so hot, then?
是工作短信嗎？
Is that a work text?
你自己腦子進水了 發錯給我了
You fucked up. You text me instead.
什麼人啊？
Who does that?
只是和朋友吹吹牛的 不是你想的那樣 我很抱歉
It's street theater, babe. It's not what it looks like. I'm sorry.
我也是
me too
我們要去小姨家
We're going to go to Auntie's house
因為爸爸要把房子維修下
because Daddy's got to do a little work on the house.
我們還有別的事要做
And we have something else to do.
- 快點 - 搞他媽什麼啊
- Come on. - What the fuck?
嘿 你
Hey, yo.
這裏對你們來說太吵了
It's gonna be too loud for you guys, okay?
- 黛比 黛比 - 把這個穿上
- Deb? Deb? - Will you put this on?
- 爸爸一起來嗎？- 黛比 你要幹嘛？
- Is Daddy coming with us? - What are you doing, Deb?
你他媽的要幹嘛？
What the fuck are you doing?
- 對你們來說會很吵的 - 老婆 老婆
- It will be too loud for you guys. - Wifey, wifey.
你認真的嗎？你在幹嘛？
Seriously, what are you doing?
爸爸和我們一起來嗎？
Is Daddy coming with us?
不會 爸爸現在沒有時間給我們
No, Daddy does not have enough time for us right now.
- 你認真的嗎？真是太棒了 太棒了  - 你能把這個放下嗎
- Seriously... That's nice. That's nice. - Can you put this on here?
嘿 甜心 媽媽其實不是那個意思 知道了嗎？
Hey, honey. Mommy didn't mean that, okay?
小甜心 過來 媽媽不是那個意思 知道嗎？
Hey, sweetie, come here. Mommy didn't mean that, okay?
她不是那個意思 好嗎？你還好嗎 寶貝
She didn't mean that, okay? Sweetie, you okay?
好 好極了
Yeah, great. Great.
過來寶貝
Hey. Come here, honey.
我現在暫時可能做不到
I'm not going to be able to make it right now,
但是晚一點兒... 好嗎
but I'm gonna come a little later, okay?
過來抱抱我
All right. Come here. Give me a hug.
- 到時間要走了 - 我靠
- Time to go right now. - Christ sake.
你慢點兒好不好
Will you slow it down a second?
讓爸爸休息會兒 他累了
Give Daddy some rest. He's real tired.
對吧甜心
- Right, hon? - What...
黛比 黛比 你能緩一緩嗎？
Deb. Deb. Deb, will you slow it down a second?
- 我們走這邊  - 黛比
- We're going to walk this way... - Deb.
注意台階   慢著
Okay, watch your step. Here we go.
黛比 慢著
Deb, can you slow it...
快點
Okay. Come on.
我們走嘍 先把你妹妹放進車裏
Let's go. We're going to put your sister in first.
好了寶貝準備好了嗎？
Here we go. Okay, baby, ready?
甜心 會沒事的 甜心 知道了嗎？
Sweetie, it's going to be okay, sweetie. Okay?
我們走
Let's go.
把你的包放這兒 你需要讓你妹妹坐這兒
Okay, put your bags in there. You wanna put your sister in the seat?
粉色的包去哪了？
Where's the pink bag?
操他媽的瘋了嗎？
Have you lost your fucking mind?
哦 在我女兒面前說這麼粗俗的話
Oh, great language right in front of my daughter.
爸爸典範！
Great fathering!
很好 很好 在我女兒面前說「操」
Nice. Nice. Dropping F-bombs in front of my daughters.
- 說什麼「我的孩子」 「我的孩子」的  - 你這爸爸當的真行
- "My kids," huh? "My kids?" - Great fathering!
我會找一個在我面前會硬的男人
Gonna find a guy whose cock actually gets hard for me.
黛比 黛比 停下來！
Deb, Deb, Deb. Stop!
請別這樣
Please don't do this.
求你了
Please.
這有點兒難 你只是現在有點兒害怕 你不知道是怎麼回事
This is a little hard. You're just scared right now, okay? You're confused.
尼克 讓開 讓開 尼克！
Out of the way, Nick. Get out of the way, Nick.
你他媽的給我滾開
Get the fuck out of here, you fucker!
你這個混蛋！
You motherfucker!
混蛋 你聽見了嗎？你這個混蛋！
You get back! You understand me, you motherfucker?
離我們遠點兒
- Stay away from us! - Nice. Nice.
很好 很好
Good. Good.
沒事 我沒事
Okay. Mommy's okay.
晚些見
See you later.
早上好
Morning
說吧
Yup
好的
Yeah
老大尼克
你一定是在和我開玩笑吧
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
看起來很疼啊
Well, that looks like it hurt.
不是嗎？
No?
早上好 各位同事
Good morning, fellow officers.
嗯 我猜他應該是壞人
I take it he's a bad guy.
你是指這個穿著黑色護甲
You mean the guy with the black body armor,
配有散彈鎗和防毒面具的人嗎？
shotgun, and gas mask?
你挺風趣啊 弄清楚他是誰了嗎？
That's very funny. We know who he is yet?
昨晚很不順？
Rough night?
是的 換個話題
Yes. Next subject?
你今天臉色很差啊
You're not looking so hot there, bubba.
我覺得他看著很棒啊
I think he looks amazing.
我體內的毒素足以把加沙地帶變成同性戀大遊行
I've got enough toxins in me to turn the Gaza Strip into a Gay Pride parade.
你還是少喝點兒「石榴汁」吧 週五尿檢
You better start downing the POM juice, big man. We've got a piss test Friday.
是週四
Thursday.
你們他媽的摩門教的人是不是這個月都在喝青草汁兒？
What, like you Mormons have been drinking wheatgrass all fucking month?
別這樣
Please.
這個你還有嗎？我快餓死了
You got another one of those? I'm fucking starving.
還有倆個沒沾上血的
Yeah, there's a couple that don't have blood.
好像就是那個粉色的 有巧克力粒兒的
I think it's one of the pinkies with the sprinkles.
這甜甜圈真是不錯啊
That's some real donut.
老兄這些太可怕了
Those are horrendous, dude.
嘿 夥計們 把警戒線往後拉點
Hey. You guys push back the perimeter.
犯罪現場需要擴大保護範圍 明白？範圍太他媽的小了
Need to extend the crime scene, okay? Too goddamn small.
- 明白 - 現在有什麼數據？
- You got it. - What's the tally?
四個當場死了 六個送醫院了
We've got four dead, six on the way to the hospital.
- 應該沒有生命危險  - 操
- But they'll be all right. - Fuck.
來買早餐的時候被埋伏了
Ambushed them as they were coming to get breakfast.
他們的車被包圍了
Surrounded the truck.
這個可憐鬼 只是想做好自己的工作
This poor fool right here was trying to do what he gets paid to do.
穿甲彈打穿了前玻璃 把他給崩出來了
AP rounds blasted through the windshield took him out.
他們搶走了卡車 加迪納警察在霍索恩跟丟了
They took the truck, Gardena police lost them under Hawthorne Municipal.
他們對路線很熟
They knew the route.
選擇加迪納是因為它就在市機場旁邊
Picked it because it was next to Municipal Airport,
因為飛行限制 所以他們知道不會有直升機追蹤
knew the restricted air space meant no ghetto bird air support.
我們面對的劫匪不一般啊 夥計們
We're dealing with a different animal here, boys.
跟裝甲卡車公司談過了嗎？丟了多少？
Talk to the armored car company? What was the haul?
他們是在去銀行的路上 幫聯邦銀行取東西
They were en route to a bank pickup for a Fed drop.
但是車上是空的
But there was nothing in the truck.
空的？
Nothing in the truck?
他們他媽的偷了倆空的裝甲卡車？
They stole a fucking empty armored truck?
是的
Yup.
為什麼開槍？
Why the fireworks?
有個受害人說車警去摸槍了 那就是開打的原因
One of the vics said the messenger went for his gun. That's when it popped off.
真是個天才！
Genius.
好吧 那輛城市四驅 有什麼線索？
Okay, the SUV, what have we got?
沒什麼有用的線索
That's a cold car.
引擎號撕掉了 車牌是偷的 沒有指紋
VIN's been pried off. Plates are stolen. No prints on it.
他們還用漂白水給它炸了
They bleach-bombed it.
好吧 把它送到科學偵察科 罩起來 棉簽全抹一遍 不放過任何細節
Right. Take it to SID. Tent that fucker. Swab it. Detail it.
操 這麼早就讓我和這個低能周旋
Ah, fuck. I can't deal with this retard factory this early.
你們誰來吧
One of you guys handle it?
兄弟 只有你了
It's all you, bro.
謝了
Thank you.
好吧 有目擊者嗎？甜甜圈店員？
All right, witnesses, donut shop guy?
他看見他們了 他們直勾勾的對視了
He saw them, and they looked right at him,
但是不知道為什麼沒動他
but, for some reason, they left him alone.
好 收集所有的監控錄像 車牌讀取器 做個大數據篩查
Okay, pull all video surveillance and plate readers. Do a Palantir run.
跟交通部門聯絡
Talk to DOT, okay?
都收集好之後 我們在辦公室碰頭
Pull it all together, and meet me at the office.
把那該死的裝甲車給我找回來
And find me that fucking truck.
老大尼克 警察血液中的原始黑幫份子
Big Nick, original gangsta cop in the flesh.
羅賓 '鮑勃'對吧？
Lobbin' Bob. Huh?
你這個網球高手還有繼續打網球嗎？
How's that mean tennis game?
看看你 夥計！
Look at you, man.
你在哪買的？很不錯的西服
Where'd you pick that up? Nice suit.
肯定不是在你消費的地方買的 那地方的東西我可買不起
Well, not where you're shopping. I can't afford it.
我說 一個小小的鎮警
I mean, how does a county sheriff
哪來的錢買這麼漂亮的夾克？
pay for such a beautiful piece of men's fashion?
這坨狗屎？這是垃圾
You kidding me? This piece of shit? Nah, this is garbage.
看看你
Look at you.
這東西太讚了
This thing's tits!
你得什麼屎勾當都幹才能買得起它吧 是吧？
You must pull all kinds of ass sporting that, no?
好吧 我不能 我不想說了..
Nick, you know what? I can't. I can't.
大清早的我可沒閒心看你在這耍猴戲
It's too early in the morning for your fucking circus.
你剛剛把一個甜甜圈扔進案發現場裏了
You just threw a donut in the hot zone.
- 我沒有吧！ - 你有！
- No. I did not. - Yeah, you did.
我扔了？那樣做太他媽錯了
I did? That was fucking wrong.
是的 我不喜歡你 尼克 也不喜歡你的辦案方法...
It was. I don't like you, Nick, or how you handle police business...
嘿 你什麼意思？
Hey, hey, hey. What's up with that?
我可喜歡你
I like you.
儘管你是個素食主義者
Aside from the fact that you're a vegetarian.
是嚴格素食者！我是嚴格素食者
Vegan! I'm a vegan.
- 素食者是喝牛奶的  - 哦 我為你感到遺憾
- Vegetarians, they eat milk... - Yeah, sorry to hear that.
你到底來幹嘛的？
What are you doing here anyway, huh?
這案子沒涉及法幣丟失 就不屬於聯邦案件
No legal tender was stolen. It isn't Federal.
暫時不是
Yet.
你定格是為了營造戲劇效果？
You're pausing for dramatic effect?
你簡直就是個大壞警官！
You're such a big, bad lieutenant.
- 我知道 我知道  - 是啊
- I know. I know. - Yeah.
我能走了嗎 老爸？我有點兒餓了
Can I go now, Dad? I'm kind of hungry.
加迪納警察來了 控制了現場
So Gardena showed up, and they secured the scene,
然後這些小丑給接手了
and then these clowns took over.
他們是誰？洛杉磯治安局的？
Who are they, LASD?
是的 他們肯定是治安局的 看看這個小丑
Yeah, Sheriff's. They must be. Look at this clown right here.
他好像是頭兒
He seemed to be in charge.
你對他有印象嗎？
You recognize him?
他在南邊玩兒過足球
He played football at South.
記得安德歐嗎？警察幹掉的菲律賓人
Remember Endo? Filipino dude the cops killed?
嗯
Yeah.
就是他幹掉的安德歐
That's the cop who blasted him.
他主管大案的
Runs Major Crimes.
要知己知彼
Get to know your enemy, boys.
洛杉磯縣警察局
誰是這團伙的頭目？
Who's running this crew?
可能有2-3人有能力做到
Probably two, three guys that can pull this off, max.
為什麼要偷一輛空的裝甲卡車？
Why steal an armored truck with nothing in it?
可能消息有誤 白幹了
Bad tip, they probably botched it.
那為什麼沒有把車扔掉？
Why didn't they dump it, then?
- 我查查廢車場 - 所有的都查
- I'll check the salvage yards. - All of them.
他們怎麼知道聯邦機構要從賭場運東西？
And how'd they know about a transfer from the casino to the Fed,
尤其是這次行程都不在常規計劃裏 他們是怎麼知道的？
especially one that wasn't scheduled through the regular carrier? How?
肯定是有內奸 錯不了
It was an inside job, bro. It had to be.
操 把止瀉藥給我
Oh, fuck. Give me the Pepto.
好吧 有內奸 那是哪個環節出錯了
Okay, inside job, but where?
賭場？銀行？還是他媽的甜甜圈店？哪個？
Right? Was it the casino, the bank, the Fed, the fucking donut shop? Where?
有沒有可能是梅利曼干的呢？
What about Merrimen?
他是什麼時候假釋的？
When did he parole again?
- 8個月前 - 8個月前？
- Eight months ago. - Eight months ago?
我們需要找到那輛該死的裝甲車
We need to find that fucking truck.
威爾森那孩子你還跟著呢麼？
Have we still got a tail on that Wilson kid?
嗯
Yeah.
就是老和梅利曼一起的那個
The one who was hanging out with Merrimen?
在哪個酒吧工作來著？
What bar did he work in?
- 哈夫布勞 - 基奇的哈夫布勞
- Hofbrau. - Ziggy's Hofbrau.
我們去會會他
Let's pay him a visit.
有Wi-Fi嗎？沒有？我們最好看看他的視頻
...some Wi-Fi? No? We better check his videos.
- 謝謝 - 沒事
- Thanks. - All right.
沃夫岡 要點什麼？
Wolfgang, talk to me.
- 唐尼 我沒錢了 - 沒事
- Donnie, I'm tapped out. - No problem.
幫我記賬上吧 好嗎？
Put it on my tab, all right?
- 當然 兄弟 我幫你搞定 - 謝謝
- Of course, man, I got you. - Thank you.
晚安
Have a good night.
我們做這票嗎？
Are we doing this?
是的 兄弟 好的兄弟
Yeah, man. All right, man.
為我們的錢和女人乾杯
To money and women.
還沒到手的
That we don't have.
你是怎麼記住那麼多人點的酒的？
How do you remember everybody's order like that?
我連我社保卡的最後4位都記不住
I can't remember the last four of my social.
不停的重複 兄弟
Lots of reps man.
我周邊的環境是被我完全掌控的 他們根本不知道
I'm in complete control of my environment. People don't even know.
- 嘿 兄弟 該走了 - 好的
- Hey, man, time to go. - Okay.
收拾收拾
Wrap it up.
- 就一點點了  - 好 好
- Just a little bit. - Yeah, yeah.
- 嗯 基奇會殺了我 - 操 喝不完了
- Ziggy's going to kill me. - Shit, not going to finish.
-給你的禮物
A gift.
小費呢？
How about a tip?
上次給了
We got you last time.
給了？
Oh, yeah, you got me last...
規矩不是這樣的
That's not how it works.
就給這點兒？ 這幫畜生
Okay, really? Zoo animals.
需要找零？
Need change?
是給你的 小妞
That's for you, Fräulein.
謝了
Thanks.
總有這麼多警察來這嗎？
Are there always so many cops in here?
我覺得他們不會選擇來這兒
Last place I'd think they'd be.
嗯 這是他們的地盤 這的酒很便宜
Yeah, this their spot. You know, cheap liquor.
嗯
Right.
這裏什麼樣的壞人都有 是吧？
Yeah, there also is a lot of shady cats in here, huh?
嗯 是的 這裏算是個中立地段吧 懂嗎？
Yeah, it's kind of neutral grounds, you know?
就像 瑞克在卡薩布蘭卡那樣 那種
Rick's in Casablanca type shit.
你在這肯定聽到了不少故事
You must've heard some stories in this place.
嗯 給他們兩杯酒 來一碟牛排
You know, give him a couple of drinks, steak on his plate,
美麗的女人纏繞
some nice women around him,
他就會告訴你他最陰暗得秘密
he'll tell you his darkest secrets.
言多必失 禍從口出
Loose lips sink ships.
說的不假啊
Ain't that the truth.
你呢？
Mmm, what about you?
在這可以釣到好多女人 對吧？
Pull a lot of pussy in here? Yeah?
說說吧
Come on.
- 我自己一個人挺好的  - 是啊
- I do well for myself. - Yeah.
我都願意操你的
I'd fuck you.
開玩笑的
Kidding.
好吧
All right.
我要走了
I'm out.
再見兄弟
See you later, man.
是啊
Yeah.
很期待再見
Look forward to it.
- 小妞！ - 操 你他媽的要幹嘛...
- Fräulein. - Dude, what the fuck are you...
唐 尼
小妞 你醒了
Fraulein, you're up. Yeah.
搞什麼
What the fuck?
還好嗎 混混？
What's up, gangster?
哦 桃子
Oh, Peaches.
哦 小妞 你起來了
Oh, Fräulein, you're up.
坐下 你就坐這裏
Sit down. You sit right there.
兄弟你走那麼慢幹嘛？
What you walking so slow for, nigga?
坐那 你就坐那
I want you to sit right there. That's you right there.
- 看這兒 那是煙  - 嗯
- Look here. There's cigarettes. - Yeah.
布若丘！
Borracho!
你們把我認錯成別人了
I think y'all got me confused with somebody.
嘿
Hey, Sporto.
想讓小妞幫你口一下嗎？
You want a blow job?
為什麼我的褲子是濕的？
Why my pants wet?
兄弟們 如果你們和這位湯姆大叔在這
Come on, man, if you and your Uncle Tom over here
玩同性戀那一套 別打我的主意
are into some homo shit, I'm good.
還不如你們現在就殺了我
Y'all just kill me now.
你自己給尿了 傻孩兒
You pissed yourself, bubba.
有時候會的
It happens.
這裏的女孩兒幫你洗了 你沒事的
I had one of the girls here clean you up, so you're good.
你抓錯人了
But y'all got the wrong dude.
你把我認成別人了
You got me confused with someone.
我現在就告訴你  我不是你要找的人
But I'm going to let you know now, I ain't the one.
你怎麼解釋？
What'd you say?
說啥？
Dude something?
我們沒認錯你 別他媽自作聰明
No, we're not mistaking you for anybody. Don't be a fucking smartass.
因為盜車17歲被捕
Arrested at 17 for GTA.
作為成人案件被審判入罪
Tried and convicted as an adult.
我們清楚的知道你是誰
We know exactly who you are.
殺人未遂在郡監獄服刑
Did a stint at county for attempted manslaughter.
加利福尼亞歷史上速度最快的超速罰單就是開給你的
Fastest speeding ticket in California history.
很牛啊
That's nice.
真他媽有才 你當時開的多快？
Fucking genius, man. How fast were you going?
每小時178公里
178.
超速狂魔啊!
Speed demon!
你和抓到你的警察是怎麼說的？
What did you say to the cop who pulled you over?
用的什麼理由？
What reason did you give him?
我說他們剛把新路面鋪好
Told him they'd just paved the road.
- 我欣賞這小子！- 有種
- I like him. - Ballsy.
我喜歡
Me gusta.
也許作為黑人你的丁丁有些小
You may have a little pecker for a black dude.
雖然你尿褲子 但是你他媽的還挺有個性的 兄弟
You may be a bed-wetter, but you've got some fucking style, buddy.
就這樣吧 女士們 該走了
All right, girls, time to go.
拿好你們的鞋啊什麼的 都走吧
Grab your shoes. Grab your shit. Let's go.
回去餵你們的寶寶們
Time to go home to your babies.
- 謝謝過來  - 不好意思
- All right, thanks for stopping by. - Excuse me.
聽好 飛車手 你已經進去兩次了
You check this out, hot rod. You're a two-striker.
看著我 我他媽跟你說話呢
You need to fucking look at me when I'm talking to you.
再犯一次錯 你就得去監獄撿肥皂了
You're one mistake away from getting sex in the ass every time you shower.
有的那些黑人和輪胎蹦一樣粗
Some of them niggas got gas pumps.
在我來看 這事聽起來挺沒勁的
Now, personally, that shit don't sound like a lot of fun to me.
你怎麼想的?感想如何？
What you think? How you feel about that?
照片裏那個男人 連我酒吧的常客都算不上
Look, the dude in that picture is not even a regular at my bar.
我看見過他幾次 但我絕不會跟這種人...
Like, I've seen him a few times, but, you know, I don't associate myself...
知道這個什麼意思嗎？
Do you know what this means?
我是一個小集團的成員
It means I am a member of a clique.
就像是個幫會
It's kind of like being in a gang.
就像是一個幫會 但是我們都有警徽
Sort of like a gang, only we have badges,
意思是你玩兒完了
which means you are done.
他沒說謊
He ain't lying.
這麼跟你說吧
Let me ask you this.
你看我們跟之前抓你的那些警察一樣嗎？
Okay, do we look like the types who will arrest you?
給你戴上手銬 把你拉到警察局那些？
Put you in handcuffs, drag you down to the station?
我他媽在問你話呢！
I'm asking you a fucking question.
一點兒不像
No. Not at all.
對 說得對
Right, exactly.
我們可以直接就把你斃了 這樣還能少寫點兒報告
We just shoot you. It's less paperwork.
所以 說吧
So tell me,
你他媽跟那幫人一起在幹嘛呢？
what the fuck are you doing hanging out in that crew?
你就是個膽小鬼
You're a pussy.
他們都是大壞蛋
Those dudes are bad dudes.
大盜 有罪之人
Great thieves but straight convicts.
梅利曼和你這種人和啤酒在幹嘛？
What's Merrimen doing drinking beers with the likes of you for?
談工作?
Talk shop?
你們要搶酒吧？
You gonna hit the fucking Hofbrau?
把地方都拆了搶那5塊10塊的2000塊錢？
Take the place down, score, like, what, two grand in ones and fives?
你們準備這麼幹嘛？我都能替你回答
Is that what's afoot? I'll answer that for you.
肯定他媽不是啊
No, it fucking isn't.
我不知道你說的這幫人是誰
I don't know what crew you're speaking about, man.
他就是到我工作的酒吧喝酒
This dude just comes to my bar where I work...
停 閉嘴
Stop. Shut up.
夠了吧 你們 我都被你們搞蒙了 就讓我...
Come on, man. This is some weird shit. Just...
聽著 操蛋臉
You listen to me, fuckface.
我們才不在乎你
We don't give a shit about you.
你是梅利曼團伙的成員嗎？
You in Merrimen's crew?
體育場那票有你一份嗎？
Huh? You hit the stadium?
你現在想說話了嗎？
You talky-talky now?
是的 求你了
Yes, please.
操!
Fuck!
我只是司機！
I'm just the driver!
他們不給我槍 我沒參與幫會活動
They don't give me no gun. I don't do no gangster shit.
他們讓我開車!所以我開車！
They asked me to drive, so that's what I do.
就那樣！操！
That's it. Fuck!
為什麼梅利曼要搶一輛空的裝甲卡車？
Why did Merrimen hijack an empty armored car?
我不知道
I don't know, all right?
他們就怕我被抓了會亂講 所以都瞞著我
They keep me in the dark for shit like this.
警察抓到我
If the cops come down on me,
我什麼都不知道就不會亂說
I can't tell them shit if I don't know shit.
你可以給我連上
Now y'all can hook me up to a lie detector,
他媽的測謊儀 你用什麼都可以
a fucking polygraph, whatever y'all got.
我知道的都告訴你們了 只有這些
I'm telling you what I know, and that's all you'll get.
求你了 放了我吧
Please, just let me the fuck go.
操 放了我吧
Fuck y'all, man. Let me go.
哇 我覺得你還挺能唬人的
Well, I thought that was relatively convincing, hmm?
好演技
Good stuff.
好吧 你什麼時候遇到他的？
All right, when did you meet him?
我能得到什麼？
What do I get out of this?
你能得到什麼？嗯 一個是自由
What do you get out of this? Well, your freedom for one.
二
Two,
你並不是壞人
you're not the bad guys.
而我們是
We are.
幾個月前他們來到酒吧
Couple months ago, they came through the bar,
我給他們倒了幾杯酒
and I served them a few drinks.
然後我們開始商議
We started talking.
嘿 唐尼 過來 夥計
Hey, Donnie, come here, man.
這是我哥們兒 博斯克
This is my boy, Bosco.
我同生共死的兄弟 我們一起服役的
My brother for life. We deployed together.
這孩子能開車
Hey, the kid can drive.
好
Okay.
唐尼 跟他講講Am系列的運輸車
Donnie, tell him about the Trans Am Series.
我開過Am系列的運輸車 就像他說的 開過4個月
Drove Trans Am Series, like he said, for about a season.
他們叫什麼？
What were their names?
夏威夷人
Hawaiian dude,
他的死黨博斯克是個白人
he had a homie, Bosco, white boy.
他之前服役過 之前在水利部工作
He was in the military, and he worked for DWP.
我跟他說我需要掙些外快
I told him I needed some extra money,
所以他給了我一個工作
so he gave me a job.
誰？梅利曼？
Who's that? Merrimen?
梅利曼
Merrimen.
雷·梅利曼
Ray Merrimen.
這人的底細搞清楚了嗎？
So what's up with this dude?
馬庫斯的人
It's Marcus' boy.
之前在哈夫布勞一起上班
Worked with him over at the Hofbrau.
在維塞德監獄一起服過刑
Say he did some time with him at Wayside.
他之前不是軍人麼？
He was a Marine for a minute.
他說能開車 就沒問題吧
Say the nigga can drive. He be cool.
好吧 我們去試探下他
All right, let's check him out.
他很聰明
Real smart dude.
我能看出他剛出獄
He had just got out of prison from what I could tell.
聯邦監獄 特米諾島  長灘島 加利福尼亞
準備好了嗎 雷？
You ready to roll, Ray?
514號
514!
來 給他戴上手銬
Come on, let's cuff them up.
你的這些破爛還要嗎？
You want any of your shit?
不
No.
走吧
Let's go.
很快再見 雷
See you soon, Ray.
你見不著了
No, you won't.
你氣色很好 寶貝
You look great, baby.
得了吧
All right. Come on.
沒開玩笑
For real.
給我帶太陽鏡了嗎
Bring any sunglasses for me?
寶貝 對不起 我忘了
Baby, I'm sorry. I forgot.
給 戴我的吧 戴我的
Here, take mine. Take mine.
不會吧
Come on.
確實是一副好眼鏡
They're good. They are.
看起來很適合你 瞧瞧
They look great on you. Look at that.
你在哪跟他見面的？
Where'd you meet him?
在卡森 夏威夷人的家裏
It was in Carson, at the Hawaiian dude's house.
卡 森
身體發力
Through your body.
- 好嗎  - 好
- What up? What up? What up? - Fucking nice.
在後面
Yeah. Fool's in back.
再來！
You're mine!
- 唐尼 有什麼好東西 兄弟  - 還好嗎？
- Donnie, what's good, man? - What's up?
- 來 跟我來  - 好 好
- Come on, man. Follow me. - Yeah, yeah.
嘿
Hey.
嗯 好嗎
Oh, shit. What's up?
- 唐尼 要啤酒嗎？- 好
- Donnie, beer? - Yeah, yeah.
謝謝 謝謝
Thank you. Thank you.
你在維賽德監獄待過？
So you spent some time at Wayside?
是的 待過一陣子
Yeah, a little bit.
每週五早上吃的是什麼早餐？
What do they serve for breakfast on Fridays?
一塊錢的那種煎餅
Silver dollar pancakes.
3個
Three of them.
你是哪兒的人？
Where you from?
霍索恩
Hawthorne.
你很會開車？
So you can drive, huh?
哦！我太會開了
Oh, I can drive.
開吧
Drive.
你也許該把安全帶繫上
You might want to put that seat belt on.
他喜歡我的車技 所以一周後我第一次參與他們行動
He liked how I drove, so, a week later, I did my first gig.
我們把體育館給搶了
We hit this rave at a stadium.
找到一個
Got one.
去掉有染料包的 其他的錢數對嗎？
Minus the dye pack, is the count all good?
對的
The count is on.
兄弟 這錢可真不少
That's a lot of money right there, bro.
我們收工吧
Why don't we just call it a day?
是嗎？
Really?
你是想只要這三摞贓款？
You want three in hot bills,
然後擔驚受怕地度過餘生？
you looking over your shoulder for the rest of your life,
還是想要30摞乾淨的錢？
or would you rather have 30 clean?
我就是說說
I'm just saying.
還是趁現在沒人查到我們 趕緊收手吧
Let's just call it quits while we're ahead.
放起來
Put it away.
我們要用這些錢弄到更多的錢
We're trading up.
好吧 去他的 我們干吧
All right. Fuck it. Let's do it.
錢去哪了？
What happened to the cash?
我不知道
I don't know.
他們不告訴我
They don't tell me.
他們也不怎麼提這事
They don't talk much.
有東西要藏的人從不會多說話
Yeah, people with things to hide never have much to say.
那我是被捕了還是說 我可以走了？
So am I under arrest, or can I leave?
還照舊生活
Nah, you just keep doing your thing.
我們會聯繫你
We'll be in touch.
嗯
Yeah?
"馬力" 8點整到中心一號 別晚了
Horsepower, be at 1st and Central at 0800. Don't be late.
你總是選這個的
You always pick the same one.
隨便挑吧 有我呢 想買啥都行
Just go for it. I'm here.Do whatever you want.
哇喔!
Woo-hoo!
指紋在加利福尼亞偵察科都鑒定過了
Ran the prints on CAL-ID.
和一個天使城的人對上了
Got a hit on our dead guy from Angel City.
- 查下你的郵件 - 好
- Check your e-mail. - All right.
叫馬庫斯 羅茲奧克蘭人
Name's Marcus Rhodes, from Oakland.
酒精、煙草與火器管理局因持槍指控而要抓他
ATF was looking for him for gun charges.
還有證明之前你說對了
And more to the point that you were making before,
他之前在二十九棕櫚村駐紮過 和梅利曼是同一時間
he was stationed at Twentynine Palms the same time Merrimen was there.
那很好 給我梅利曼的檔案
This is good. Give me the book on Merrimen.
看你的右邊
Look to your right.
知道那是什麼嗎？
You know what that is?
是專管銀行的銀行
It's the bank for banks.
是聯邦銀行在洛杉磯的分行
Los Angeles branch of the Federal Reserve.
這是唯一一個沒有被打劫過的銀行
It's the only bank that's never been robbed.
附近的所有街道都安裝了聲音和圖像檢測儀
All the surrounding streets are wired for sound and image.
只要你站在馬路對面看著銀行超過2分鐘
Stand across the street and stare at the building for two minutes,
就會有保安禮貌的請你離開
you'll have security on your ass asking you politely to leave.
如果他們在那看見你第二次
If they see your face again,
全國所有的特勤部門人員都會來調查你
every Secret Service agent in the country is going to be looking for you.
這裏無縫可鑽
The place is case-proof.
有53次試圖潛入的案例
There have been 53 break-in attempts.
沒有一次能越過大堂
Not one has got past the lobby.
很有挑戰 而我們要搶的就是這家
That's why we're going to rob it.
好 我們來看看
Okay, here we go.
拉古拉 尼格奧 是06年進去的
Laguna Niguel was in '06.
他被捕後被送到維克托維爾舒監獄
Got caught for that, get sent up to USP Victorville SHU
直到16年6月 給我下未破案的文檔
until June of '16. Now give me the unsolved book.
你一進入到大堂
As soon as you enter the lobby,
電腦就會自動在全國罪案聯網上核對你的資料
computers run you through every law enforcement database in the country.
如果你有未處理的停車罰單
If you've got outstanding parking tickets,
在你未接觸到第一級的保安之前他們就都查清楚了
they're going to know about it before you get through the first level of security.
所有員工都有門禁卡
All the employees wear security swipe cards
這樣他們就可以出入第一道人工檢查關卡
that grant them access through the first set of man-traps.
出入是極其森嚴的
Access is severely restricted.
地下二層就是保險庫樓層
Two stories below street level is the vault floor.
順便說一句
By the way,
這個嫌犯
uh, his crimey...
- 拉沃爾 - 拉沃爾
- Levoux? - Levoux.
- 他和梅利曼一起服過役嗎？
He serve with Merrimen?
不止 他們在長灘工藝學校的時候一起踢過足球
Not only that, but they played football in high school at Long Beach Poly.
- 你沒跟我開玩笑吧 - 沒有
- You've got to be shitting me. - No.
中央保安系統 就是聯邦的中樞神經
Central Security, it's the nerve center for the Fed.
這裏就是裝甲車出入裝卸錢箱的地方
This is where the armored cars come in, drop off the money tubs.
錢箱會直接交給聯邦的員工
Money tubs are handed off to the Fed employees.
那裏一直都儲有5000到8000億美元
At any one time, there's anywhere between 500 and 800 billion dollars in there,
每一寸都被攝像頭和動作感應器所覆蓋
every millimeter of it covered by cameras, sensors, and motion detectors.
他們都擅長什麼？
Yeah. What did they specialize in?
這是我在二十九棕櫚村人力資源找到的資料
I got this from the HR desk at Twentynine Palms.
近身突擊隊 兩人都在中東真槍實戰過
Close Quarter Battle Unit. Both saw combat in the Middle East.
拉沃爾是爆破專家 梅利曼是實戰士兵
Levoux specializes in explosives, where Merrimen specializes in soldiering,
兩人都是海軍陸戰特種兵快擊手
both MARSOC fast Marines.
但是裏面是有圈套的
But there's a hitch.
每一張鈔票的序號都是記錄在聯邦的資料庫裏的
The serial number of every bill is recorded in the Fed's database.
如果任何一張不見了 不管是為什麼不見
So, if a note goes missing,
他們都能知道是哪一張
they're going to know exactly which one it is.
鈔票會被聯網標記 只要那張鈔票
They're going to flag it. If that bill comes up again,
在世界任何的一個角落再出現
whoever recirculates that cash, no matter where they are in the world,
他們就能找到持有鈔票的人
that person can be tracked.
那啄木鳥博斯克呢？
Okay. Bosco, the peckerwood?
亨廷頓海灘男孩 也是海軍陸戰特種兵
He's a Huntington Beach kid, also MARSOC Marines.
他做過他們的聯絡員 前途光明
He did comms with them. He had a solid career.
但是他並沒有和其他幾人一起服役
But he didn't serve together with the other guys.
梅利曼在維克托維爾的時候 他是他們的代言人
He was the Wood Rep at Victorville when Merrimen was there.
他們就那樣混到一起的
That's where they linked up.
唐尼做了一年半的士兵然後退伍了
Donnie was a Marine for a year and a half, then discharged.
我覺得
So, the way I see it,
這夥人就是這樣走到了一起
that's the way all these niggas ended up working together.
我只看到這兩個關聯點 足球和服役
There's only two passports on the streets, sports and military.
每次聯邦從銀行接手存儲金
Every time the Fed receives a deposit from a bank,
第一件事就是把錢都送去點鈔室
first thing they do is send that money up to the count rooms.
錢被塞進點鈔機
They run the notes through the counting machines.
兩個目的
They're accomplishing two things here.
一 他們要再次檢查數目是否準確
First, they're double-checking the accuracy of the bank's deposit.
如果多了少了
If the bank is off at all,
就會在賬戶上做對應錢數的增減
they're going to credit or debit the account accordingly.
二 他們把新的鈔票和舊的損壞了的鈔票分開
Two, they're separating newer, fit currency from old unfit bills.
最重要的就是 他們會把廢舊了的鈔票序號從系統裏刪除
But most importantly, they're erasing the serial numbers
序號被刪除
of the old bills from the Fed system.
那些鈔票對政府和整個世界來說
Once those numbers are erased, to the Fed, to the rest of the world,
就已經不存在了
that money has ceased to exist.
我們來看看未偵破的案件
Wait, let's look at the unsolved cases.
04年的好萊塢博勒國家銀行搶劫案
In '04, you have the Boller National Bank Hollywood job, okay?
他們是在下水道挖了通道
They tunneled through the sewer system.
很老練的 技術含量高 有人做內應 沒破案
Sophisticated, skill set, someone with access, unsolved.
05年 有弗爾特裝甲車被劫案
Okay, in '05, you have the Fuerte armored car depot job.
用聚能藥包炸開了保險庫
Blew the depot vault with shaped charges.
光一百美元點鈔室
In the $100 count room alone,
每天就有3億美元被變成廢紙
an average of $30 million is designated as unfit every day.
每天下午4點到5點之間
Between 4:00 p.m. and 5:00 p.m.,
所有費錢就會被運到粉碎機裏
all the cash gets shot out to the shredder.
全都被銷毀了
It's all destroyed.
3億美元...幾秒內就灰飛煙滅了
$30 million turned to dust in seconds.
然後聯邦的合作垃圾公司
It's then picked up by the Fed's waste management company
會把粉末運到垃圾場扔掉
and brought out to the dump.
如果我們能在這些廢鈔被送進粉碎機
If we can get to those unfit bills
之前拿到它們 並全身而退...
before they go to the shredders and get out clean...
我們就能拿到可以安全使用的3億美元
You got $30 million nobody is looking for.
答對了
Bingo.
06年 有拉古拉 尼格奧  跟之前一樣
In '06, you have Laguna Niguel.
只是這次梅利曼不走運後車燈壞了
Same thing, only this time Merrimen gets unlucky with the tail-light.
服刑直到2016年 在他服刑期間
Goes to prison till 2016. Now in that time, while he was in prison,
我們遇見過多少個純熟 執行的極好的搶劫案呢？
how many highly sophisticated, well-executed heists do we have?
沒有！但是你思路很對 繼續說！
None, but you're on a roll. Keep going.
甜甜圈的收銀員 目擊了整個過程
The counter guy at the donut shop? Witness to the whole thing.
他們為什麼要放過他？
They left him. Why?
因為他們只打軍裝 不會傷害無武裝的平民
Because they shoot uniforms, not unarmed civilians.
那就是他們以前訓練出來的結果
Exactly what they were trained to do.
普通黑社會小混混？他們可不是
Gangbangers, these are not.
這些就是我們要找的人
Okay, these are our guys.
只要我們抓住他們 所有案子就都破了
We nail these guys, we solve all these cases.
就是這個團伙
This is the crew.
你還沒有告訴我們要怎麼通過安保
You still haven't told us how you can get past that security.
我們不從這裏進去
We're not going in this way.
我們從那兒進去
We're going in that way.
那小妞呢？
What's going on with Fräulein?
我們隨時可以逮他
We can move on him anytime we want.
蒙特利公園
- 我只給最低工資 - 好
- I pay minimum wage. - Okay.
每單外賣佣金3美元 小費你我平分
Plus $3 for delivery. And you split the tip with me.
週三11點開工
You start Wednesday, 11:00.
謝謝你
Thank you.
我不喜歡那的食物 但是我還可以去
I don't really like the food there, but I'm down to go,
- 但是你得買單 - 我才不幫你買單呢
- but you've got to pay this time. - I'm not paying it.
啥
What?
- 他媽每次都是我請 - 啥？
- I pay every fucking time. - What?
別那麼吝嗇了
Get off your wallet, buddy.
我今天忘帶錢包了 孩子們 對不起了
No, I forgot my wallet today, boys. I'm sorry.
- 又忘帶？- 又？
- Again? - Yeah, again.
你是鱷魚臂
Got an alligator arm.
我用5美元賭黑傑克 掙了160
I sat down at blackjack with $5, and I made $160.
尼古拉斯 奧 布萊恩？
Nicholas O'Brien?
幹嘛？
Yeah?
我建議你收下這個
I suggest you take these.
你被法院傳喚了
You're being served.
你開玩笑嗎？
You kidding me?
沒有
I'm afraid not.
什麼事？
What's going on?
兄弟 你還好嗎？
You all right, bro?
額 我想我可能要離婚了
Yeah, I guess I'm getting divorced.
他說「離婚」？
He say "divorced"?
嗯
Yo.
歡迎加入俱樂部
Welcome to the fucking club.
去處理的你事情吧 大佬
Now, go handle your business, big man.
上車
Gas the jet.
操
Fuck.
這是近距離細節
There's a closer view.
4天前這裏有個停電盲點
There was a rolling blackout in this quadrant four days ago.
對 上幾個月他們經歷了好多次
Yeah, they've been happening a lot over the last few months.
嗯
Okay.
他們對外說他們有備用電 其實根本沒有
They say they have full backup power, but actually they don't.
- 他們進入節電模式 - 優先供電
- They go into brown-out. - Yeah, prioritize the grid.
肯定是優先給保險庫 所以保險庫很完好
Priority, of course, is the vault. So everything in there stays intact.
但是外圍的所有東西 比如走廊的攝像頭
But anything that is peripheral, like cameras in the hallway,
點鈔房裏的碎紙機都沒電了
shredders in the count rooms, everything else cuts out.
但是要預測下一次停電的時間簡直是天方夜譚
To time it during another rolling blackout is going to be fucking impossible.
- 所以你想搞一次人為停電？- 我們行嗎？
- So you want to simulate it? - Can we?
潛入 讓他們有兩分鐘進入節電模式
Break in, have them go brown for about two minutes.
我們假設可以 但我需要更多的數據才能確定
I'd say yes, but I'd like to have data to be sure.
很好
Great.
我們一旦進入了點鈔室 只有攝像頭要擔心了
Once we breach the count room, only thing left is the cameras.
他們是自帶電源的
They run on their own power supply,
他們不會被節電模式所影響
so they're unaffected by the brown-out.
解決辦法就是用電磁脈衝波
The solve here is we run an EMP burst.
應該可以廢掉9米之內的監視器和動作感應器
Should take out the cameras and motion for about 30 feet.
這些信息是從哪裏得來的？
Where you get all this information from?
你不需要知道
You don't have to worry about that.
你只需要知道信息很可靠就行了
Just trust me when I say it's solid.
勾線做的怎麼樣了？
How we doing with the Telecal hook?
還需要幾天 應該不是問題
Couple days. Shouldn't be a problem.
你需要多少人支援？
How many handlers do you need?
我現在在B大門
Uh, gate B right now.
大搖大擺的走向聯邦儲蓄
Strolling right into the Federal Reserve.
武裝人員離開B卸貨口
Force leaving loading dock B.
聯邦儲備銀行  洛杉磯分行 中央安保
身份證？
ID?
簽字
Sign in, please.
必須隨身攜帶這個 用第二區域的電梯
Keep this on you at all times.
到2層的用餐區
Second bay of elevators. Cafeteria's level 2.
他沒問題 讓他進去吧
Buzz him in. He's good.
挺香啊
Smells good.
他沒事 讓他進去
He's good. Let him in.
- 莎倫？- 是我
- Sharon? - Mmm-hmm. That's me.
- 你好 - 你今天好嗎？
- How you all doing? - Good. How you are doing today?
- 他挺帥的 - 謝謝
- He's fine. - Thank you.
她可釣不到你
She ain't getting none.
閉嘴！別這樣
Shut up. Really?
- 祝你一天愉快 - 我可不插嘴了
Y'all have a good day. I'm gonna stay out of it.
- 肯定會愉快了 - 祝你一天愉快
- We will now. - You have a wonderful day.
午餐 甜點 午餐 甜點...
Lunch. Dessert. Lunch. Dessert.
再見 甜心
Bye, sunshine.
他出來了
There he goes.
美聯儲那邊沒發現問題
Fed's got 82.
也許這是他常規送餐路線之一
Maybe it's part of his regular route.
給美聯儲送中餐
Delivering Chinese to the Fed,
拉倒吧你
my left nut.
才不是呢 他們在查看內部情況
No. They're casing the joint from the inside.
我們回顧下所有案件
Okay, go back.
除了現金
Other than cash,
他們從體育館裏的賭場還偷走了什麼？
what else do they take from the casino in the stadium?
美聯儲存款單
Fed deposit slips.
- 但這些可能都是跟現金一起被偷的 - 也可能不是
- But those were probably in with the cash. - Or not.
聽我說 有沒有可能他們是用偷現金
Listen, what if they were taking the cash
是為偷其他東西而打的掩護？
to disguise the fact that they were really there for something else?
然後他們搶走了一輛空的裝甲車 想想啊 哥幾個
And then they take down an armored car that's empty. Come on, guys.
回想下唐尼是怎麼說的
Look, remember what Donnie said.
他們要弄更多的錢 他們將會有大行動
It's trading up. They're going big.
嘿 尼克 美聯儲可不那麼容易搞定吧
Hey, Nick, you can't take down the Fed, man.
抱歉 梅利曼可不是傻子 這絕不可能
I'm sorry, Merrimen's no dummy. It's impossible.
搶劫美聯儲就如奧運會奪金 而梅利曼就他媽是卡爾·劉易斯
The Fed is the Olympics, and Merrimen is Carl fucking Lewis.
我告訴你們
I'm telling you,
小妞沒跟我們說實話
Fraulein's holding out on us.
我的天
My gosh.
- 他來了 - 好的
- Oh, he's here. - Okay.
- 天哪 你看起來太美了 - 謝謝
Damn, girl looking fine.
你看起來很棒
Thank you. You look amazing.
你好
How are you?
- 你看著真棒 - 謝謝
- Looking good. - Thank you.
- 這是我媽媽 這是奧蘭多 - 嗨
- This is my mom. This is Rolando. - Hi.
- 很高興見到你 我是奧蘭多  - 嗨 我是瑪莉亞 很高興見到你
- Nice to meet you. Rolando. - Hi, I'm Malia. Nice to meet you.
- 我現在知道你這麼美是遺傳誰了 - 謝謝
- I see where you get your looks from. - Thank you.
謝謝
Thank you.
- 我來拿著這個 - 好
- Can I take that? - Oh, yeah, sure.
奧蘭多 這是我爸爸
Um, Rolando, this is my dad.
你好嗎 拉沃爾先生 很高興見到你
What's up, Mr. Levoux? Nice to meet you.
我想跟他單獨說兩句話
Let me holler at him for a second.
- 來 我跟你談談
- Let me talk to you, bruh.
寶貝 別擔心 他們只是說幾句話而已
Honey, don't worry about it. Okay? They're just gonna talk.
這麼跟你說吧
So here's what's up.
在過去的16年裏
For the past 16 years,
保護女兒的安全是我的責任
my daughter's safety and protection has been my responsibility
也是我唯一的責任
and my responsibility only.
而現在 在她一生中 這是第一次我要把這責任交給別人 也就是你
Now, for the first time in her life, I see I've got to hand you that responsibility.
別搞砸了
Don't fuck up,
不然在你會讓你媽媽每天以淚洗面
or your mama will weep as she has
推著坐輪椅的你潦度殘生
to wheel your ass around every day the rest of your life.
我有練習過這段話 因為我想用最和氣的口吻對你說這些
Now I worked on this, because I want to say this to you as nice as possible.
你明白嗎？
Do you understand?
是的 先生
Yeah. Yes, sir.
沒事 沒事
It's all right. It's all right.
聽著
Listen. Listen.
他只是想說很高興見到你
All he's trying to say is, it's wonderful to meet you,
他想祝你有一個美好的夜晚
and he wants you to have a beautiful evening.
今晚11點半見？
I'll see you at 11:30.
知道了
Yeah. Yeah.
- 11點半 11點半 - 這就對了
- 11:30. Yeah. 11:30. - Good choice.
我想他搞清楚情況了 兄弟
I think he got the picture, bro.
托倫斯
啤酒和清酒 走著！
Beers and sake, let's go.
- 喝酒 - 搞什麼的
- Have wine. - What the fuck?
嘿
Hey.
兄弟
Buddy.
唐尼 對嗎？
Donnie, right?
怎麼了？
- Yeah. - Yeah.
我那天在健身房見到你了
Yeah, spotted you at the gym the other day, yeah?
嗯 你怎麼樣
Yeah, man. How you doing?
兄弟們 好嗎？
What's up, fellows?
你之前在長灘工藝學校踢球？
You play football at Long Beach Poly?
你看著眼熟
You look familiar.
不是 我不是這裏的人
No, I'm not from around here.
你來這幹什麼？上班嗎？
What are you doing here? You work around here?
我來這享受晚餐
Enjoying my dinner, man.
- 真的？- 是的
- Really? - Yeah.
這的東西多難吃啊
Food here sucks.
我們都是來這撩妹的
Yeah. Yeah, we come here for the ass.
那健身房見吧
So I'll see ya at the gym, man.
好的
Yeah. Definitely.
祝你今晚愉快
Have a good night.
你是55號吧 我記得你的號碼
Number 55, right? That's how I remember you.
你跟我一樣是55號 對吧？
We wore the same number, 55, right?
我去過南托倫斯
I went to South Torrance.
我們跟你們打過幾次比賽
Yeah, we played you guys a couple of times.
你隊裏有不少薩摩亞肥佬
You and all those fat-ass Samoans.
這幫肥佬體格大 還很懶
Yeah, they were big, but, man, lazy motherfuckers.
我們把你們虐成狗
Probably all that Spam.
我帶隊時就虐你們
Yeah, we fucking crushed you guys.
你帶隊也是挨虐
Crushed you guys when I was there. Crushed you guys when you were there.
你們一直被我們虐
Still crushing you guys.
我哥們都在這呢
We've got family here, bro.
你要是能自己出去就最好不過了
Don't really appreciate you popping off.
好吧 別激動 沒必要這樣
All right. All right, man. No need to get all agro.
我剛才說話傷人嗎？
Was I being rude? Was I being rude?
- 什麼？- 走吧 該點菜了
- What? - Let's go order, bro.
兄弟 聽我說
Hey, look, man, listen.
你這幾個哥們真不錯 沒人想惹麻煩 我們這就走
You've got a beautiful family. Everything's all good. Excuse us.
走嘍
Kampai.
健身房見了 唐尼
See you at the gym, Donnie.
女士們 祝你們今夜玩得開心
Have a good night, ladies.
你是警察嗎？
You a cop?
不是 你是嗎？
No. Are you?
下車
Get out of the car.
那邊走
Go!
你把竊聽器藏哪了？
- Where's the wire? - Come on, man.
我他媽身上沒有竊聽器
I'm not wearing a fucking wire, man.
我說我他媽身上沒有竊聽器
Man, I'm not wearing no fucking wire.
起來
Get up.
他怎麼認識你的？
How does he know you?
別跟我說你倆是他媽在體育館認識的
Don't tell me it's from the fucking gym.
我跟他不熟
Look, I don't know him.
崩了他吧
Smoke this punk.
說實話 你這混賬
Talk, motherfucker.
我不是警察
I'm not no cop, all right?
是他過來跟我說話的 他認識你
Now he came to me. He know you.
他認得你們所有人 我什麼也沒跟他說過
He know all of you. But I ain't tell him shit.
他嚇唬過我 然後我就再也沒見過他
He was sweating me. I ain't seen him since.
我以為他不會來找我們了呢
I thought he'd leave us alone.
他們知道多少？
So how much do they know?
他們什麼都不知道
Nothing.
我什麼都沒說
I ain't tell them shit.
我也什麼都不知道
I don't know nothing anyway.
你知道我是值得信任的
And you know I'm the last person that would fuck this up.
如果任務取消 我能理解
Now, if we've got to call it off, I get it.
但是我什麼也沒跟他說
But I know I ain't tell them shit.
告訴他我們週五行動
Friday. Make sure he knows it's on.
羅靈丘陵莊園
真不錯
So good.
是真的 真的
It's true, though. It's true.
好的
Okay.
最近還好嗎 尼克？
How you doing, Nick?
- 我是尼克 - 你好
- I'm Nick. - Hello.
- 你好啊 - 好
- How are you? - Good.
嘿 晚飯..
What's for...
- 晚飯吃什麼？- 尼克 你喝多了吧
- What's for dinner? - You smell like alcohol, Nick.
放鬆
Relax.
我來之前已吃過了
I already ate.
給我拿根筆 老兄
Give me a pen, stud.
尼克 我本想給你打電話的
Nick, I was gonna call you.
我原想請你吃飯
I was gonna take you to dinner next week.
趕緊給我他媽拿根筆
Just give me a fucking pen.
謝了 拉德
Thanks, Rudd.
- 我還是去... - 給我坐下
- I'm gonna hit the... - No, you're not.
酒好喝嗎？
How's the wine?
好喝嗎？
Good?
這酒挺他媽好喝啊
That's pretty fucking good.
我想我就...
So I imagine I just, uh...
隨便找個地方簽名就好了
What, just sign anywhere, yeah?
是嗎？
Okay.
如果你敢碰我的女兒
And I imagine it's assumed that if you were ever
敢跟他們說話
to touch one of my girls or, say, talk to them
哪怕只是看他們一眼...
or, you know, even look at them,
我就會...你懂的吧？
I go boom-boom. You know what I'm saying?
我這說得夠明白了吧？
But, I mean, that's self-evident, right?
我想我剛才說的就不用寫進合約裏了吧?
There's no need to put that in the contract, is there?
- 尼克 - 我可不這麼想
- No, I didn't think so. - Nick...
請你現在離開好嗎 尼克？
Can you please go, Nick?
- 鬧夠了吧 尼克？- 當然
- That's enough, Nick. - Sure.
起來
Come on.
起來 跟我擁抱一下
Come here. Give me a hug.
這樣我們就不用費錢做心理咨詢了
Come on. We'll save a fortune in therapy.
跟我擁抱一下啊
Come on. Give me a hug.
這才對嘛
There you go, huh, hoss?
什麼事你都搞成種場面嗎？
You've just always got to make a spectacle out of everything.
這才對嘛
There you go.
差不多吧
Yeah, pretty much.
好了 尼克 我想你該走了
All right, Nick. I think it's time to go.
好了 尼克 走吧
Come on, Nick, let's go.
報警啊你們
Call the fucking cops. That's what I'm saying.
我很抱歉 但你真的得走了
- Call the fucking cops. - I'm sorry, but it's time for you to go.
快報警
Call the cops.
- 很抱歉 - 你別他媽碰我
- I'm sorry... - Don't fucking touch me.
- 抱歉 - 別碰我
- I'm sorry. - Do not fucking touch me.
- 行了 尼克 - 請你快走吧
- Come on, Nick. - Just, please go.
忘了問你了...
By the way...
- 你想怎麼樣？ - 你是跟她玩的後入式的嗎？
- What do you want? - You hitting that from behind,
啪啪啪的時候還在想她紋的什麼？
and you're wondering what that thing is on her ass?
- 告訴你 紋得是哥的名字  - 尼克 快走吧 求你了...
- It's a tattoo of my name. - Nick, please...
"老大尼克·奧布萊恩"
"Big Nick O'Brien."
就是給你提個醒
Just a heads-up.
嘿
Psst.
別忘了打電話約哦
Call me.
你們慢慢來
Take your time.
你經歷了什麼？
What happened to you?
博拉科 你看我這身怎麼樣？
Borracho, what do you think?
你他媽之前說那堆話是什麼意思？
What the fuck was that?
你在健身房看到我了？
You spotted me at the gym?
別激動 好吧
Tranquillo. All right?
坐下
Sit down.
這衣服我要了
I'll take it, Freddy.
我跟他單獨聊一會兒 好吧？
Just give us a minute, okay?
現在警察查得緊 他們不敢殺你的
Look, they're not going to off you with this much heat, okay?
他們什麼時候行動？
When's this happening?
週五
Friday.
在哪？
Where?
我不知道 我只知道他們週五行動
I don't know yet. All I can tell you is Friday.
感謝上帝今天已是星期五了
TGIF, huh?
你會保護我的 對嗎？
You're protecting me on this.
小妞
Fräulein,
我們會保護好你的 兄弟
we got your back, bro.
不用擔心
Don't worry about a thing.
操
Fuck.
你們最好穿防彈衣
Better wear your vest.
準備行動吧
We're in.
英格爾伍德
Z?
皮科裏維拉銀行 在蒙特貝拉中心
Pico Rivera Savings, Montebello Town Center.
收到 8點見
Copy that, boss. See you at 0800.
把信息告知全組成員
Tell the crew.
我按你說的做了
I did what you told me to.
星期五
玩的開心嗎？
You have fun?
他對你還好吧？
He treat you right?
瑪洛阿
Maloa.
你知道我是愛你的 是吧？
You know I love you, right?
我也愛你
I love you, too.
去吧 上學去吧
Come on, go to school.
幹得漂亮
There you go. Good job there.
麥坎娜
McKenna!
嘿 寶貝
Hey, sweetie. Hey, sweetie.
你最近怎麼樣 還好嗎？
How are you? Good?
你在這幹嘛呢？
What are you doing?
我正要去上班 路過此地
Well, you know, I was on my way to work
所以就想來看看我的小猴子
and thought I'd come by and say hello to my little monkey.
行不？
Is that okay?
在學校怎麼樣 還好？
How's everything at school? Okay?
- 是啊 還好 - 是嗎
- Yes, it's good. - Yeah?
你阿姨家怎麼樣
And what about Auntie's house?
你媽媽和卡西還好吧？
Mommy and Cassady, are they good?
你的玩具熊呢 還好嘛
What about the honey-bear? Honey-bear good?
你想我了嗎？
Yeah? You miss me?
好啦 小寶貝 回去上課吧
All right, Pookie, better get back to class.
我什麼時候還能見到你？
When am I going to see you again?
快了 寶貝 就快了
Soon, sweetheart. I'm gonna see you soon.
我想回家
I want to come home.
我也想
Me, too.
好了 你快回去上課吧
All right, you better get back to class, okay?
再見啦
But I'm gonna see you later.
你保證會再來看我？
Promise?
我保證
I promise.
來 擊拳為證
Come on.
休息結束了 孩子們都回來吧
Recess is over. Come on, kids. Come line up.
回去吧 寶貝
Go on, Pookie.
老爹 再見
Bye, Daddy.
快點 麥坎娜
Come on, McKenna.
快點 親愛的
Come on, honey.
帶好武器
Jock up.
換上裝備 老哥
Tac up, brother.
不搶聯邦儲備局了？
No Fed?
計劃有變
Change of plans.
聽好
Pay attention.
除非必須開槍打人 否則你的手指一定別放在扳機上
Always keep your finger off the trigger until you're going to shoot somebody.
如果必須開槍 先得打開保險
If and when that happens, safety selector switch.
一下是半自動 兩下是全自動開火
One for semi, two for full auto.
準備好彈夾
Mag release.
沒子彈就換彈夾
Out with the old, in with the new.
檢查彈夾是否裝好
Tug it. Make sure it's in there good.
然後給槍上膛 準備下一輪射擊
Slap the bolt home, you're ready for round two.
不開槍的時候 槍口一定對準地面
Other than that, keep this thing pointed at the fucking floor.
- 懂了嗎  - 明白
- You understand? - Got it.
穿戴好裝備
Go put your shit on.
- 博拉科 給我來個彈夾 - 好的
- Magazine, Borracho? - Yeah.
- 準備好了？ - 是的
- We good? - We good.
蒙特貝羅
嫌疑犯已到既定位置
Suspects arriving on location.
我們沒有證據給地區檢察官看 他們還沒展開犯罪行動
We've got nothing for the DA. They haven't committed a crime yet.
他們搶完銀行我們就動手抓人
They clear the bank, we take them down.
- 各單位就位 - 收到
- Stand by. - Roger that.
大白天的
Broad fucking daylight.
他們全副武裝
They're packing big.
靠 看看這群混賬東西
Ooh, shit. Look at these motherfuckers.
全都趴下 全都趴下
Get down on the ground! Get down on the ground!
趴下 全都趴下
Down on the ground! Get down on the fucking ground!
都別動
Freeze!
都別動 呆在那
Freeze! Don't move! Stay right there!
都別動
Freeze!
- 你們兩個 去那邊  - 去那邊
- You two! Move! Get over there! - Get over here!
速度快點
Hurry up!
滾出來 速度快點
Get out here, now!
快點
Move there now! Go! Go! Go!
別動 待在那別動
Move back! Stay right there! Now!
臉對著地趴好
Eyes to the floor!
聽好
Listen up!
大家都聽好了
Everybody pay the fuck attention!
低頭趴好
Eyes to the ground!
我只說一次
'Cause I'm only going to say this once!
如果你們合作 聽從指揮
If you cooperate, if you follow directions,
我們就絕不會傷害你們 我們只圖財 不想殺人
you will not be hurt. We are here for money, not for you.
所有人都出來沿著櫃檯趴好
I want everybody lined up on the counter. Let's go!
快點
Move down!
Move down! Let's go!
速度快點 櫃檯後面的也都出來 快
Everybody behind the counter, come out front! Let's go!
把頭低下 別亂看也別亂說話
Keep your eyes down and your mouths shut.
聽我命令
On my command,
把兜裏的手機都給我拿出來
reach inside your pockets, remove your cell phones,
然後舉起手來
and put your hands in the air.
所有人 向前兩步
Everybody take two steps forward.
都跪下
Now go down on your knees.
手機都扔進來
All right! Cell phones right in here.
都老實點
On me.
快點 手機都扔進盒子裏
Let's go. Put them in the box.
把他們手捆上
Tie them up.
快快快
Go! Go! Go!
誰也別逞英雄
There will be no heroics today.
老實地呆著
You guys go ahead and get comfortable.
你們得在這呆一陣子了
We're going to be here for a while.
有想去上廁所的
Anybody need to use the bathroom?
往褲襠裏尿吧
Take a piss on yourself.
你 起來
You. Get up.
別動
Stop.
坐下
Sit down.
我需要你冷靜下來
All right, I need you to calm down right now.
嘿 跟你說話呢 看著我
Hey! Look at me.
深呼吸
Take a deep breath.
好
Good.
我知道你已經按過無聲警報器了
I know you already triggered the silent alarms.
所以我需要你拿起電話
So I need you to pick up the phone,
撥打911後 按我說的跟警察說...
dial 911 dispatch, and explain the following.
你得把我的話寫下來
Go ahead and write this down.
這裏發生211案件 劫匪有人質
There's a 211 in progress, and we have hostages.
在一小時內 他們得給我送來一千萬美金
Within one hour, they need to deliver $10 million
必須都是未標記的小面額鈔票
in unmarked small denomination bills to this bank
要用警局直升機運來 加滿油
inside a department helicopter loaded with fuel.
跟他們說 不滿足我們的要求 每隔一小時 我們就殺死一名人質
Tell them we plan on killing one hostage every hour until our demands are met.
不允許警察接近銀行
No cops are to approach the bank.
如果安排談判專家來 他敢張嘴
And if a negotiator even tries to contact us,
我就馬上殺死一名人質
we will automatically kill another hostage.
聽懂了嗎？你都記下來了嗎？
Is that clear? You got it all?
打電話吧
Go ahead and pick up the phone.
有外勤警隊暫時沒任務嗎？
Any available units, we have a bank 211 in progress...
他媽的
Shit.
在皮科裏維拉銀行發生搶劫案 地址是蒙特貝拉
...at the Pico Rivera Savings in Montebello
威爾考克斯路和亞特蘭大路岔路口 2891號
at 2891 Wilcox and Atlantic.
- 嫌犯都有武器 - 該死 這幫混蛋
- Suspects are armed... - What the fuck?
劫持人質 拒絕談判
...and have taken hostages and are refusing a negotiator.
他們在幹什麼？這不是他們的以往手法啊
What the fuck is going on? That's not their MO.
向總部匯報 我們就在案發地點監視
Call in, tell them we're on scene, have suspects under surveillance,
讓他們都撤退
and to back the fuck off.
我們是洛杉磯縣治安官 我們正監視嫌犯
This is LASD, we have surveillance on the bank. Stand down.
請下令所有警隊小組撤退 我重複 全部撤退
I repeat, have all units stand down.
靠 我都聽到警笛聲了
It's bullshit. I can hear them already.
你們他媽的在幹什麼？
What the fuck are they doing?
停車
Stop!
出來
Get out!
你們他媽的在幹什麼？
What the fuck are you guys doing, huh?
混蛋
Asshole!
你們他媽的在幹什麼？
What the fuck are you doing? What's going on?
你監視著嫌犯 還讓他們控制了銀行和人質？
You were running surveillance, and you let this shit go down?
這是我們的案子 我們監視他們好幾個星期了
It's our fucking case. We've been surveilling these guys for weeks.
監視他們
That's what surveillance is!
就是想在他們犯罪的時候抓捕他們
They commit a crime, and then we stop them.
走 去金庫
Go. Go to the vault.
把金庫打開
Open it.
我們走 來
Let's go. Come.
在這坐下
Sit. Sit down.
我開免提
I'm going to put this on speaker phone.
你來接電話 但不能說名字
You're going to answer, but don't use any names.
懂嗎？
You understand?
你好
Hello?
你好 我們是洛杉磯警察
Hello, this is the Los Angeles Police Department.
跟我通話的人是誰？
Who am I speaking with?
我是這的分行經理
This is the branch manager.
我需要跟匪徒頭領說話
Sir, I need to speak with the person in charge.
我聽著呢
You are.
好 我先自我介紹下 我叫...
Okay, good. Well, let me introduce myself. I'm Officer Parada...
老子不在乎你是誰 我們要求的東西 你們都準備好了嗎？
I don't give a fuck who you are. Are our demands being met?
現在跟我說話的是誰？
Who am I talking with now?
回答問題
Answer the question.
我們正在準備
It's being worked on as we speak.
但請你理解一下...
But you need to understand...
你害死了一名人質
You just killed a hostage.
該死的
God damn it!
- 起來 - 不要啊
- Get up. Get up! - No! No! No!
起來
Come on, move!
我什麼也沒做 求求你 你要幹什麼
I didn't do anything. Please. What are you doing?
求求你 不要殺我
- Come on. - No! No! No!
該死
Fuck!
- 媽的 - 都在你們掌控下？
- You were on it, huh? - Shit!
你這蠢貨
You're so full of shit, O'Brien...
你知道他們的條件
You heard the demands, you stupid motherfucker!
還派談判專家聯繫他們？
- Yeah. - You put a negotiator on? Christ!
- 去你媽的 - 你罵我？
- Fuck you! - Fuck me?
罵的就是你
Yeah, fuck you!
你自己犯傻
Fucking nice haircut, you fucking idiot.
你他媽還推我？
Who are you fucking pushing now?
你他媽開玩笑呢？
Are you fucking kidding?
- 立刻聯繫特警到現場 - 你這混蛋
- Get SWAT rolling right now! - You fucking pussy.
你這傻逼還生氣了？
Fucking Lobbin' Bob is angry!
- 好了 老大 我們走 - 他媽的
- All right, boss, let's go. Let's go. - Shitheads!
- 我們走吧 - 媽的
- Let's go. - Fuck!
案子這邊有新情況發生
We've got a situation going on...
媽的
Shit!
梅利曼 你在幹什麼呢？
What the fuck are you doing, Merrimen?
說吧
Yeah?
我們是警察 請別掛斷電話
This is the Police Department. Please don't hang up.
我叫丹尼
My name's Danny,
只有負責與你聯繫 除了我沒人會打電話給你
I'll be your only contact. Nobody else is going to call you.
你是劫匪頭領嗎？
Is this the person in charge?
我是分行經理
This is the branch manager.
代表劫匪頭領跟你說話
I'm speaking on the man in charge's behalf.
分行經理 你叫什麼？
Do you have a name, branch manager?
聽著 他們已經殺死了一名人質 是個女的
Listen. They've already killed one of the hostages. A woman.
他們不會跟你聯絡
They will not speak to you again.
如果在他們的要求未滿足前 你再打電話來 他們還會殺死一名人質的
If you call back again before their demands are met, they'll kill another.
趕緊把他們要的東西給他們吧
Just send what they want.
錢和直升機在準備了
The money and the chopper are en route,
都需要時間來安排
but it's going to take a little bit of time.
我需要至少90分鐘 可以麼
You need to give me at least 90 minutes. Is this doable?
可以 別再打電話了
Okay. Don't call back.
這個區域是哪裏
What's the prefix here?
長灘 562區
562. It's Long Beach.
你好
Hello?
你在看嗎？
You watching?
是的
Yup.
你準備如何脫身呢？
So how the hell are you going to get out of this one?
我還沒想好呢
Not sure yet.
你從那個妓女那要到的我的電話號？
Did you get my number from her cell?
休想讓我戴上手銬
I ain't cuffing up.
無所謂
That's okay.
反正我今天沒帶手銬
I didn't bring my cuffs anyway.
是啊 我看到了
Yeah, I can see that.
是他嗎？
Was that who I think it was?
是的
Yup.
直升機到位時
We've got a chopper that's gonna come down.
會在這裏降落
The chopper is going to land right over here.
圖上顯示有一個雙門入口 兩個單門出口
I've got two-door entry on one. One-door entry on two.
準備引爆
Breaching!
他們把金庫大門炸開了
Well, they just blew the vault.
發生什麼了？
What the fuck?
這裏是美聯儲 您是哪裏?
Federal Reserve, accounts receiving.
我這裏是阿拉米達
Hey, it's Al at Alameda.
從皮科裏維拉銀行要運過來一批錢
We have a drop at Pico Rivera we need to schedule.
您看安排週三下午兩點接受如何？
How's Wednesday at 2:00?
可以的 安排在18號下午兩點 是嗎？
That works. You're confirmed for 2:00 p.m. the 18th.
是的 非常感謝
Great. Thanks.
- 我們在這 對吧？- 是的
- We're here, yeah? - Yeah, that's us.
這是什麼？
So what is this?
是污水管道
This is the sewer line,
如果圖紙沒錯的話 這都是水泥管道
and according to this map right here, it's all cemented up.
直升機申請進行到哪一步了？
Hey, where are we with the chopper?
還在等審批
We're waiting on clearance.
別擔心 反正他們也跑不了
Relax, they're not going anywhere.
還等個毛審批 我們必須行動了
To hell with clearance. We've got to move.
奧布萊恩
O'Brien, hey!
他是不是出門忘吃藥了？
Is he off his meds?
跟他說讓他趕緊滾回來
Tell him to get the fuck back here!
能別嗶嗶了嗎？
Will you shut the fuck up?
去你媽的
Oh, fuck you.
我們得去支援他
We better go back him up.
尼克奔正門去了 我們得去支援
Nick's heading to the front. We're on the move.
行動
Here we go.
我了個去 他是認真的嗎？
- Fuck! - Is he serious?
大家都還好嗎？
Everybody okay?
是的
Yes.
求求你 老天 救救我吧 我想再見到家人
Please, Lord, please, let me see my family again.
- 尼克你在哪？- 洛杉磯縣治安官
- Nick! - Sheriff's Department.
尼克？
Nick!
這裏安全
Clear!
我這也安全
- 他媽的 - 尼克 你在哪？
- The fuck? - Nick, what's your location?
你在哪？
What's your location?
你好 還是阿拉米達給您致電 我不記得
Hey, this is Al at Alameda again.
達皮科裏維拉銀行出庫的時間了
I forgot to schedule a drop at the Pico Rivera Savings.
你們今天安排的是幾點來著？
What do you have open today?
"黑貓" 我是"白貓" 時間確認了嗎？
Ghetto Bird, this is Silverback. We confirmed?
確認了 是兩點四十五 也就是兩分鐘之後
Check. Appointment's at 2:45. That's in two minutes.
運往皮科裏維拉銀行
Pico Rivera.
"馬力" 一切都準備就緒了嗎？
Horsepower all set?
是的 都準備妥當了
Yeah, I'm ready to go.
你們是新來的？
They got you on a new route?
是啊 這周剛給我們調過來
Yeah. Yeah, they just switched us over this week.
好的 給我看看你們的證件
All right. Let me get you guys' IDs, man.
好的 給你
Yeah, sure. There you go.
好了
All right.
你們可以過去了
You're good to go.
- 謝謝 - 打開大門 過去吧
- All right, thank you. - Open the gate. Have a good one.
該死
Oh, fuck.
皮科裏維拉銀行2.2？
Pico Rivera Savings? 2.2?
是的 是我們
Yup, that's us.
把錢車推上來吧
Bring her up.
準備 1 2 3拉
All right, ready. One, two, three.
- 在這簽字 - 好的
- Sign here. - You got it.
馬克 你是新來的？
You're new here, Mark?
是的
Yes, sir.
你們來的有點晚啊
You guys running a little bit late.
是的 我們來的時候有點堵
Yeah, we ran into some traffic, so...
我不知道你倆以前在哪運鈔
I don't know where they had you guys routed before,
但是在我們這 交接時間是非常嚴格的
but we run a tight, tight ship around here,
如果你們要遲到了的話 必須先打電話通知這裏一聲
so, if you're going to be late, have base call it in.
沒問題 這次是我工作有失
Yeah, no problem. That's my fault. I just...
記住下次打電話
Just have them call.
跟我來吧
On me.
嘿 路易吉 阿拉米達那批錢運到了 你去接受吧
Hey, Luigi. Alameda's on deck. Check them in.
收到
Copy that.
是新人
New guys.
我出去看看
I'm going to step out for a minute.
哥幾個你們好啊
How you guys doing today?
- 你好 - 你好
- Good. All right. - Good.
嘿 你好嗎？
How you doing?
- 還不錯 你呢 - 我也很好 謝謝
- All right, how are you? - Good, thank you.
請在這裏簽字
Sign that for me, please.
都是百元面值的嗎？
All hundreds?
第一車裏的都是百元面值的 第二車什麼面值的都有
The first one's all hundreds. The second one is mixed.
我們這邊有點忙不過來
We're a little backed up.
好的 盡快就行
All right, do what you can.
你們先等等 喝杯飲料什麼的吧 非常感謝
Guys want to hang out, get a Coke or something? Appreciate you.
謝謝
Thank you.
我們需要方圓250米地下管道檢查權限
We're going to need access to the recording off-site.
能搞定麼
Can you get that to us?
- 瞭解  - 你需要看心理專家
- Understood. - You need professional help.
說得對
Desperately.
剛才是我不對 這現場交給你了
My bad last time. Your crime scene.
"白貓" 我是"馬力" 我已就位
Silverback, this is Horsepower. I'm in.
"綠貓" 我是"白貓" "馬力"已就位
Greenpeace, this is Silverback. Horsepower is in.
收到 "白貓" 現在關燈
Roger that, Silverback. Lights out.
好吧 我們去看看
Okay, here we go.
強尼 又他媽斷電
Johnny, we're fucking brown again, man.
停止一切工作 讓他們離開點鈔室
Got to shut down. Pull them out of the count rooms.
停電了
We're going brown.
我們要關閉一會兒 所有人去休息10分鐘吧
We've got to shut down for a bit. All teams go ahead and take 10.
路易吉 出來吧
Luigi, come on.
好的
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
根據斷電應對程序 他們都撤出去了
They went to brown. They're clearing out.
- 我們去把門都鎖好 - 好的
- Let's lock it down. - Copy.
準備行動
Get ready to go.
啟動電磁脈衝
Powering up EMP now.
全部檢查完畢
All clear here.
可以行動了
Good to go.
外面安全了 你出來吧
You're clear. Go.
好像這出了點問題
Shit. Check something out.
你覺得是哪裏壞了？
What do you think it is?
百元面值鈔票計數室的攝像頭壞了嗎？
Are the cameras up in the 100 room?
壞了
Uh, negative.
555-01-43. 555-0143.
他們太慢啦
It's taking too long.
這裏是訂餐熱線
Tasty Orders.
我是美聯儲的莎倫
This is Sharon at the Fed.
我一個半小時前定的餐
Now, we ordered almost an hour and a half ago.
我們午休都要過了怎麼還沒送來？
Now, I only have so much time on my lunch break.
在路上了 馬上就送到
It coming! Be there in a few minute!
他們剛打電話給中餐館
They just called for the Chinese.
動作快點
Hurry it up.
動作感應警報也失靈了嗎？
Motion is out in there, too.
是啊 供電還沒恢復呢
Yeah, man, we're still brown.
我們得重寫程序 趕緊啟動
You know, we better override. Power it up.
是啊
All right.
搞定了
Done.
讓他們重新數一遍錢
Okay. Better get that count, too.
糟糕 警衛過來了 快藏好
Shit, here comes security. Get down. Get down.
我們得檢查一下百元面值鈔票計數室 動作感應警報失靈了
Hey, man, we got to check this 100 count. Motion went off.
路易吉你聽到了嗎？
Luigi...
快按住對講鍵 讓他們不能說話
Step on it. Step on it, quick.
怎麼了？
Yeah?
- 路易吉 - 該死
- Luigi. - Yeah?
路易吉 你佔著線呢兄弟
Damn, dude! Luigi, you're stepping on the line, man!
拉塞爾你說什麼
Say again? Russell?
嘿 笨蛋 你得鬆開按鍵才能說話
Hey, dumb-dumb. You've got to let go of the push to talk.
收到 我去找他
What the hell is going on here today?
路易吉一直聯繫不上
Luigi, man. He's stepping all over the line.
這傢伙手忙腳亂的
He's hot-micing like a motherfucker.
他在食堂呢 去找他吧
He's in the cafeteria. Go ahead and get him.
好的 收到 我過去看看
All right. Roger that. I'm stepping out.
你安全了 快動手
You're clear. Go.
老天爺啊
Holy shit.
路易吉 你一直不鬆開對講鍵呢
Luigi, you're hot-micing.
你得鬆開按鍵才能說話
You've got to let go of the talk button. You're stepping on the line.
嘿 我沒一直按著對講鍵
Dude, it's not me.
我們得重新數一遍百元鈔票 叫上你的搭檔
Come on, we've got to check the 100 count. Let's go. Get Junior. Let's go.
轉到五號線了
Switch to line five.
你還有不到2分鐘的時間了 速度快點
You got about a minute and a half, two minutes. Let's go.
他們回來了 趕緊撤退
They're back. Get out.
路易吉 你看到什麼了嗎？
Luigi, you see anything, man?
什麼也沒看到
Yeah, we're good. There's nothing back there but dust.
你讓我來看什麼？
What am I looking for?
沒事 我要找點樂子 你再數一遍錢
Don't worry about it, man. I'm gonna juice up the room. Run the count,
- 確保沒有任何問題 好嗎？- 收到
- and make sure we're good, all right? - Copy that.
你在哪？
Where are you?
我是"馬力" 我在排氣管道裏呢
This is Horsepower. I'm in the vents.
"綠貓" 你那邊任務結束了 撤吧
Greenpeace, you're done. Cut out.
電力恢復了
We are back up, brother.
全體注意 回到鈔票計數室
All teams, back to the count room.
通知洛杉磯警局中心
Get on with LAPD Central.
我們在第八和格蘭大道上 跟蹤監視嫌犯
Tell them we're running surveillance at 8th and Grand.
代碼5 不要驚動嫌犯
Request a Code 5. We do not wanna spook the suspects.
收到 代碼5已生效
Copy that. Putting in a Code 5.
是我記錯了嗎 我怎麼記得這裏原來是裝滿錢的？
Am I tripping or was this full before?
我們再數一遍吧
Let's just check the count.
是712200美元嗎？
$712,200.
是的
拉塞爾 錢數沒錯
Russell, the count is on.
好的 收到 去查阿拉米達運來的錢吧
All right, roger that. Go ahead and clock out Alameda.
去數阿拉米達運來的錢
Take Alameda out.
錢數沒錯
The count was good.
但你兩個錢箱都是半滿的
But both of your bins were half-full.
你說什麼？
Sorry?
你兩個錢箱都是半滿的
Your bins, they were half-full.
給我的時候就是這樣
That's how we got them.
下次來時 這點錢裝袋子裏就行
Next time, just put it in a cash sack.
不用這麼麻煩的
Makes things a lot easier.
用腦子工作 別蠻幹
Try and work smart, not hard.
好主意 謝謝
Okay, sounds good. Thanks for the advice.
我們本來想給你小費的 但是你來得太晚了
We would tip you, honey, but that just took too damn long, okay?
我們飯店只有我一個送餐的 抱歉了
I'm the only guy they've got delivering today. I'm sorry.
抱歉 哥們 我還得看一下你們的運鈔文件
Sorry, guys, let me see your drop confirmation again.
- 好的 - 給你
- All right. - There you go.
中餐餐館的？
Chinese food guy?
讓他進去
Go on. Buzz him in.
讓他在那等著
Hold him there.
2:45
讓他過來
Yeah, send him through.
過來一下 小伙
Come here for a sec, buddy.
我沒看到你進來時的簽名呢
Yeah, man, I don't have you signed in.
你叫什麼？
Where's your name?
我簽字了啊 你上一班的人看著我簽的
Come on, man, I signed my name with a dude from the last shift, man.
我不知道怎麼跟你說
I don't know what to tell you.
這飯菜可真"好吃"啊
Damn you finicky.
- 我得讓他們退我錢 - 對
- I'm getting my money back. - Okay.
確認完了
That's all I need.
好了 你們可以走了
All right, you boys are good to go.
- 非常感謝 - 放鬆些
- Thank you very much, Officer. - Take it easy.
- 祝你今天愉快 - 好的
- You have a good day. - All right.
- 行吧 你走吧 - 再見
- Go on. Get out of here. - Thank you.
請幫我接大廳警衛
Yes, security in the lobby, please.
這裏是大廳警衛
Lobby.
你看到那個送餐的了嗎
Yeah, did you see a delivery guy?
他是個淺膚色黑人 穿著紅色上衣 差不多一米八高
Red shirt, light skin. About 6 foot.
- 怎麼了？- 別讓他走
- Wait, what? - Stop him.
你們負責左側 我們負責右側
You got eyes on the 1-2 side? We'll cover the 3-4 corner.
收到
Copy that.
我剛在警衛崗耽擱了一下 你在哪？
Got held up at security. What's your location?
在格蘭南大街 剛過弗農大道
South on Grand, just past Vernon.
右轉上了蓋奇大道 右轉上了蓋奇大道
Go right on Gage. Right on Gage.
收到
Copy that.
下車 速度快點
Move! Let's go! Get out!
- 下車 速度快點 - 別激動
- Come on, move! Move! Here we go! - It's cool.
- 快下來 - 別激動
- Come on, get down! Go! Go! Go! - It's cool. I'm cool, man.
別激動
Be cool, bro. Cool.
操
Fuck.
他在那 紅衣服的那個 往前開兩個路口
There he is. There he is. Red shirt. Two blocks ahead.
發現嫌犯
Eyes on suspect.
他正向9點鐘方向奔希爾大街去了
Walking eastbound on 9th, approaching Hill, south side of street.
在前面截住他
Pull up in front of him, in front of him.
抓住這個王八蛋
Let's get this motherfucker.
先把他抓進車裏來
Let's ram his bitch-ass into the gate first.
他媽的上車 滾上車
Get in the fucking car! Come on. Get in.
他媽的
Fuck.
揍他
Hit him!
媽的 別亂動
Motherfucker.
太平洋地平線垃圾站 南大門
速度點 盡快完事好撤退
All right, let's go. Let's go. Let's get it done as quick as we can.
你他媽的
Little fuck.
那個混蛋在哪？
Where is he? Where the fuck is he, asshole?
混蛋
Fuck.
把耳機給我拿下來 那混蛋在哪？
Fucking... Fucker!
把一次性電話交出來 他在哪
Give me the burner phone. Where the fuck is he?
太平洋地平線垃圾站
Pacific Horizon Salvage.
南門 他們在那集合
In South Gate. That's the rally point.
我是"白貓" 說吧
Silverback, go.
"馬力"被抓了
Horsepower's burned.
再說一遍 我聽不清
Repeat that. I can't hear you.
"馬力"被抓了
Horsepower is burned.
他廢了
He's done.
我現在還安全 我去哪跟你們匯合？
I'm still clean. Where am I going, bro?
該死
Fuck!
速度快點 錢你們都收好了嗎？
Let's go. Let's go. You guys got it all?
- 是的 都在這了 - 好的 都帶走
- Yes, it's all in. - Pick it up.
好的
It's good.
太平洋地平線垃圾站 在阿拉米達支路附近
Pacific Horizon Salvage. South Gate, Alameda Corridor.
收到 我馬上跟你匯合
10-4. Headed to you.
其他人怎麼樣？了
What happened to the other two?
都被抓了
They got burned.
發現嫌犯
Eyes on suspects.
黑色四門雪佛蘭巨無霸
Black, four-door Suburban!
我們正沿著哈羅大道向南開
Heading southbound on Alameda.
馬上到勞森大道了 你們在聖達非跟我匯合
Approaching Slauson Avenue. I need you to parallel me on Santa Fe.
前面堵車了 怎麼回事？
We got some traffic up ahead. What's going on?
路堵死了
Corridor's backed up.
我們剛從阿拉米達支路出來 正往南開
We just turned down Alameda Corridor, heading south.
該死
Shit.
正在接近嫌犯 嫌犯在6點鐘方向
Coming up on suspect, six o'clock.
真堵
Shit.
右翼隊伍正在接近
Right lane is closed up ahead.
我重複 右翼隊伍正在接近
I repeat, right lane is closed up ahead.
看到了嗎？
You guys see that?
20 30輛車後面的那車是警察嗎?
Twenty, 30 cars back. What is that?
是警察嗎？
Is that...
好了 停車
Okay, we're at a stop, stop, stop.
等不了支援部隊了 我們得行動了
Fuck backup. We've got to move now.
該死
Fuck.
是的
Yup.
是警察
That's them.
- 給我防彈衣  - 好的
- Give me my vest. - Yeah.
好的 給你
Yeah, here we go.
他們堵在那了 我們得在交通順暢之前抓住他們
Okay, we've got them pinched in. We've got to move before it opens up.
給他戴上手銬
Cuff him up.
注意 嫌犯有防彈衣
Be advised, suspects wearing body armor.
不要瞄準軀幹射擊 瞄準四肢和頭部射擊
No center mass shots. Limb and head shots only.
收到 往那邊開
Copy that. Go around right here.
都卡住了
It's jammed up.
準備好了麼 出發
Good? Okay, let's go.
- 該死 - 怎麼了？
- Oh, shit. - What?
他們從車裏出來了
They're getting out of the car.
Z 去右翼包抄
Z, go down the right.
格斯 博拉科跟我走中路
Gus, Borracho, center with me.
默夫 你在左翼 別往上衝
Murph, stay on the left. Don't come in.
- 把自動步槍給我  - 操
- Pass me the saw. - Fuck.
我們上
Let's go.
趴下
Stay down. Stay down.
Get down. Get down.
- 縣治安官 趴下 - 趴下
- Sheriff's Department. Stay down. - Get down. Get down.
- 趴下  - 縣治安官 趴下
- Get down. - Sheriff's Department, stay down.
趴下 躲在發動機後面
Get down. Get down. Stay by the engine block.
趴下 躲到方向盤後面去
Get down behind the wheel.
縣治安官 女士 回到車裏去
Sheriff's Department. Lady, get in the car.
該死
Oh, shit.
博拉科
Borracho!
換位置
Moving!
Moving.
格斯和默夫 你們穿過去截住他們 可以吧？
Gus, Murph, you two go across and cut them off, okay?
托尼•Z 準備好了嗎？
Tony Z, you ready?
上
Let's go.
換位置
Moving!
上
Move!
換位置
Moving. Moving.
換彈夾
Mag change!
換位置
Moving.
換彈夾
Mag change.
換位置
Moving!
快走
Go! Go!
托尼 你怎麼樣？
Tony, you okay?
- 上 上 - 你沒事吧
- Yeah, go! Go! - You okay?
該死
Fuck!
快跑
Go!
掩護他
Cover!
快跑
Move.
該死
Fuck!
他在磚牆那邊
Brick wall! Brick wall!
他跑到磚樓後面去了
Behind the brick building!
我的孩子
My kids...
你跑不掉了
You're in His hands now.
聽懂了嗎？
You hear me?
該死
Fuck!
別逼我
Don't do it.
早跟你說過了吧
Told you.
是啊 你說過
Yeah. You did.
什麼鬼
What the fuck?
你看這個
You see this?
幫我都打開
Here. Do those.
該死
Oh, shit.
他們弄這東西做什麼 雪景球嗎？
So what? They were going to make fucking snow globes?
做一萬個？
Like 10,000 of them?
去看隊員們怎麼樣了沒？
You check on the boys?
我會去醫院看一眼他們
Yeah, I'm going to roll to the hospital.
你要給博拉科的妻子打個電話嗎？
You gonna call Borracho's wife?
打啊
Yeah.
好的
All right.
他們本計劃去海港的
This won't go to Harbor.
你失去了一個夥伴 我深表遺憾
I'm sorry you lost one of your guys.
謝謝
Thanks.
你還好嗎？
You all right?
我還好
Yeah, I'm okay.
我沒事
Yeah.
尼克 你得戒煙了
Nick, you've got to stop smoking, man.
試試這個
Here.
有機的哦
It's organic.
這些都會歸功給聯邦調查局 你知道的吧？
You know everything was accounted for at the Fed, right?
當然知道
Apparently so.
唐尼在嗎？
Hey, is Donnie around?
他辭職了
He quit.
你在附近有再見到他嗎？
So you haven't seen him anywhere?
我說了 他辭職了
I said he quit.
兩天前辭的
Two days ago.
要來瓶啤酒嗎？
You want a beer?
一瓶哪夠 我想喝50瓶
Very much so. Like 50.
- 謝謝  - 不客氣
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
你看到單位新來的小妞了麼？
Did you see that new chick? Little fat-ass?
就是臀部很性感的那個？
The new girl who works down the hall?
哥幾個最近怎麼樣？
What's going on, gentlemen?
哥們 你還 真高興你能來
- Gentlemen, good to see you. - Yo!
- 你好嗎？- 你妻子知道你來這裏嗎？
- Good to see you. - Your wife know where you are?
你是怎麼拿到這份工作的
How did you get that job?
你真的會數數麼
Can you actually count?
我能控制整個環境
I'm in complete control of my environment.
沒人能知道我怎麼做到的
People don't even know.
聯邦儲備銀行洛杉磯分行
他媽的小妞
Fucking Fräulein.
倫 敦
各位兄弟
What's going on, boys?
還好嗎？都還不錯嘛？
How you doing? You good?
要喝點啤酒嗎？
Some beers?
嘿 服務員
Hey, guv.
給我這些哥們上酒
A round of beers for my mates.
你想喝什麼？
And for you?
我要求不高
I'm easy.
想不到喝什麼
I don't know.
你幫我選個好的吧
Surprise me.
好的
I can do that.
- 乾杯 - 乾杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
你為什麼找我？
So why you come to me?
你很兇悍
You're a beast, man.
而且除了你也沒人能幹成這事
Plus, you're the only one that can pull this off.
聽著
Listen.
如果我答應幹這票的話 就得我說了算
We do this, I call the shots.
得用我的人 這票算是我的 不是你的
My crew, my job, not yours.
懂了麼？
Got it?
- 我懂 - 就得這麼來
- Completely understand. - That's the way it has to be.
就這些
That's it.
這都是我的寶貝
It's my baby.
我就弄到這些
That's what I've got.
你怎麼弄到這些的？
How did you get a hold of all this stuff?
你在酒吧就能弄到這些東西？
You got this all at that bar?
我費了很多時間才收集到這些的
Collected it over time.
哇哦
Wow.
這是超人才能幹的活
Job for Superman.
乾杯
Cheers.
謝謝 我很喜歡別人叫我公主
Thank you. I love when you call me Princess.
你在街對面上班嗎？
You work across the street?
是啊
Yeah.
在鑽石交易所？
Diamond exchange?
是啊
That's right.
這酒算我請你的
Beer's on me.